[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What does it really mean in the bigger context of our election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Oh, I think it's a little early to tell for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carter"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Do you actually mean that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I was asked by somebody if I thought that the current president was the weakest president, and I said I thought the competition probably was President Carter, that the two presidencies did not have the energy or the leadership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "What does America, what does President Obama actually do when you have great powers like Russia and China saying we're not playing ball?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, it's a tough situation for the United States and for the administration.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America", "Russia", "China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Russia"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "If you were President Obama, what is the thing that you do to stop right now any more of these atrocities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "The idea that sanctions will work as long as Iran and Russia and other countries are supportive of the Assad regime is mindless.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "If I was to pin you down and say, what was your greatest moment in office and your worst moment, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Oh, I think probably the worst moment is being engaged in a war.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "How important is it to any political leader, do you think, to have that kind of person at their right-hand side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Oh, I think any -- any person in tough jobs is so fortunate to have someone who can walk up to them and call them by their first name and tell them what they really think, and add some balance and perspective and dimension to a life that gets quite hectic sometimes when you're serving an important position.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Do you think you've built up a reputation that is perhaps not entirely accurate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Oh, goodness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Your thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- it's not really surprising that the secretary would say something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "How are you claiming some kind of weird victory out of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "There's nothing weird about flipping the state senate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Are they all a bunch of mad extremists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Were you choking on your soup?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "ASSERMAN SCHULTZ: Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Was his opinion correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "And a big defeat for the Democrats, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Could Mitt Romney pick him as a VP?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "MITH: I don't think so, because I think part of Romney's message is going to be about how he united both parties in Massachusetts, got things done as governor.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "When the Democrats squeal about money, are they being disingenuous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "They are completely being disingenuous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "Ford"], "PERSON": ["Donald Rumsfeld", "Carter"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "I think you also have to remember that Donald Rumsfeld lost his job -- first job in the White House from the Ford administration to the Carter administration.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Do you quibble?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Completely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "If Iraq was a disaster, then what was Libya?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Let me stop you in full explosive flow.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "On the foreign policy stage, very hard to see many negatives, isn't it, for President Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, he actually increased the troop numbers in Afghanistan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rumsfeld", "Obama"]}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What do you think the smart thing for Obama to do is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I think Rumsfeld did have a point, that all of this talk of sanctions does not seem to be effective, that the choice Obama faces is whether or not to intervene militarily or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Yet what do you do about the humanitarian catastrophe that is unfurling before our eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I don't think you've seen any politicians, any sort of leading national politicians with a clear answer to that question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]